http://www.opinioncenters.com/privacy-policy

JOIN OUR RESEARCH PANEL
We’re always looking for people to participate in market research studies – your opinion counts. Learn more about the studies we conduct and join our panel to get paid for your opinions.
Your Opinion Counts
Opinion Centers of America is part of a large company that conducts market research for a variety of industry-leading brands.
If you're interested in sharing your opinion and getting paid for your suggestions, join our panel of study participants today.
JOIN OUR PANEL
Focus Groups
We recruit participants, host, moderate and review results.
In-depth Interviews
We talk with traditional households, distributors, executives and more.
Emotional Testing
We measure emotional reactions to offline and online products and services.
Eye Tracking
We help our clients see what their customers see—or don’t see.
Contact Us
Questions? Just ask. We’re here to help.
If you’d like to submit a new research project request, please give us a call or email us directly. You can also review our full suite of Research + Customer Experience offerings.
Call Us
800-779-3003 or 440-779-3000
Email Us
oca@opinioncenters.com
Like us!
Join our Panel
Thank you for your interest in joining our database! We’re looking for all types of people to participate in market research studies – your opinion counts. Please complete the form below to join our research panel. Once your information is in our database, we’ll contact you if you qualify for one of our studies.
Your privacy is important to us.
The information you have provided below is kept strictly confidential and will be used by Opinion Centers America to help identify potential study participants. If at a later time you choose to no longer be identified as a potential participant for future surveys, you can unsubscribe from our database.
If you are selected to participate in the survey process, prior to your participation we will seek your explicit consent for us to share or sell any information gathered or recorded resulting from your participation in a given survey.
For additional information, please view our Privacy Policy.
1
Contact Information
2
Personal Information
3
Employment & Education
4
Review
Contact Information
First Name
Last Name
Maiden/Prior Last Name
Where are you located?
Home Street Address
Suite / Apt.
City
State
Select a State/Province
Alabama
Alaska
Arizona
Arkansas
California
Zip Code
How can we reach you?
Primary Phone Number
Secondary Phone Number
Email Address
Confirm Email Address
Additional information about you.
living situation
Choose One
RentOwnOther
How did you hear about us?
Choose One
EmailFacebookFlyerOrganization/ClubReferral-Word of MouthReferral-Opinion Centers America Business CardWeb AdsWebsite-Opinion Centers AmericaOCA EmployeeClient List
Have you worked with us before?
I'm new to your database of panel participants.
I'm already in your
database, just updating my information.
Next
Personal Information
Gender
Select
Male
Female
Birthday
Month
January
February
MarchAprilMayJuneJuly AugustSeptemberOctoberNovemberDecember
Day
Day
12345678910111213141516171819202122232425262728293031
Year
Year
1920192119221923192419251926192719281929193019311932193319341935193619371938193919401941194219431944194519461947194819491950195119521953195419551956195719581959196019611962196319641965196619671968196919701971197219731974197519761977197819791980198119821983198419851986198719881989199019911992199319941995199619971998199920002001200220032004200520062007200820092010201120122013201420152016201720182019
Ethnic background
Choose One
African AmericanAsianCaucasianHispanicOther
Marital Status
Choose One
MarriedDivorcedSeparatedWidowedSingle, Never MarriedDomestic Partner
Do you have children under 18 years old living at home?
Yes
No
Please list your children‘s gender and birth dates, if under 18
Childs Gender
Choose One
Male
Female
Childs Birthday
Month
JanuaryFebruaryMarchAprilMayJuneJuly AugustSeptemberOctoberNovemberDecember
Day
Childs Day
12345678910111213141516171819202122232425262728293031
Year
Childs Year
2001200220032004200520062007200820092010201120122013201420152016201720182019
add child
remove child
Political Preference
Choose One
DemocratRepublicanIndependentOther
Do you own a Smart Phone?
Choose One
NoYes, iPhoneYes, Android
Are you a smoker?
Choose One
Yes
No
Previous
Next
Employment & Education
Highest level of education completed
Choose one
Some High SchoolTechnical SchoolHigh School GraduateSome CollegeCollege GraduateSome Graduate SchoolGraduate Degree
Household income before taxes
Choose One
$25,000 or less$26,000 - $35,000$36,000 - $50,000$51,000 - $75,000$76,000 - $100,000$101,000 - $150,000$151,000 or more
Industry of employment
Choose One
AgriculturalArt/DesignAutomotiveBusiness OwnerCall CenterClericalConstructionConsultingEducation/TrainingEngineering/ArchitectureEntertainmentFinance/BankingFood GovernmentHealthcareHospitality ServicesHuman ResourcesInsuranceIT/Computer Software/HardwareLegalManufacturing/ProductionMarketingMedia/PublishingNon ProfitReal EstateRetailSportsTrade/LaborTransportationUtilities/Oil & GasVeterinary ServicesOther
Current occupation
Teachers, indicate grade level(s) taught.
Current Employment Status
Choose One
Full-TimePart-TimeHomemakerStudentRetiredNot employedDisabled
Current health insurance provider
Choose One
AetnaAmbetterAnthem Blue Cross/Blue ShieldAssurantCignaHealthSpan Inc.HumanaInHealth MutualKaiser PermanenteMedicaidMedicareMedical MutualUnicareUnited HealthcareUnitedHealthOneOther
Previous
Next
Review
Contact Information
Personal Information
Employment & Education
I have read and understand my responsibilities as a participant and I agree to the terms and conditions above.
Do not sell my personal information
Please check the box above to be added to our participant database. Your privacy is important to us, and your information will never be sold to, accessed by, shared with, or given to anyone outside of Opinion Centers America.
Previous
Submit
Thank you for Submission
Scroll to topIcon by RRD
